http://www.hampers.co.uk/privacy-and-security

News
Welcome to Hay Hampers!
Hay Hampers
my cart:
item
£0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Subtotal: £0.00
ALL GIFTS
Search:
GO TO SIMPLE CHECKOUT
GO TO ADVANCED CHECKOUT
Ship to multiple addresses?
OUR PRIVACY NOTICE
This Privacy Notice explains which types of your personal data we collect by using Hay Hampers, Italy2eat and Vintners websites, and how we handle the data.
WHO THE DATA OWNER IS
The data controller is Hay Hampers Ltd, who is also referred in this policy as “we” or “us”. Only some of your personal data (such as recipients’ addresses and phone numbers) will be shared with our couriers in order to successfully deliver your order. Data is not shared with anyone else.
WHAT DATA WE COLLECT
We collect: notes from all our conversations with you, details of any complaints or comments you make or purchases you have made, items viewed or added to your basket, web pages you visit and how and when you contact us, in order to provide you a better quality tailored service. We will need to collect some personal information from you in the event of you placing an order: first and last names, email address, billing and postal addresses, recipient address and phone number.
HOW WE COLLECT YOUR DATA
Directly:
-          When you buy from us and you create an account on our website
-          When you subscribe to our newsletter
-          When you contact us
-          When you use social media to communicate with us
Indirectly (using third party service, see below):
-          When you browse our website
WHERE YOUR DATA IS STORED
The data we collect is stored in our system. You can ask us at any time to delete it. Alternatively, you can do it yourself, e.g. unsubscribing from our newsletter. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to sales@hampers.co.uk. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
HOW LONG WE STORE YOUR DATA
Data will be stored for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected.
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA
We know how important it is to keep your data safe. That’s why our website is using ‘https’ technology. This means all your transactions are secured and trusted, and sensitive data such as payment card information is protected. All data sent to our server and the data returned to you is encrypted to prevent unauthorised persons viewing your details. To view the security certificate check your browser settings.
You can be confident when you enter 'My Account' with your email address and password, that all your information in the Checkout and Payment area will be fully encrypted using the latest Secure Socket Layer security technology.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
THIRD PARTY SERVICES
We use a third party service (Google Analytics) to improve the customer experience. This is intended to help us understand website traffic and usage; data is stored on Google servers in the United States and are not shared with anyone else but Hay Hampers Ltd.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
COOKIES
To improve your experience on our website we also need to collect your cookies. A cookie is a piece of information shared between a website and your computer's hard drive. This is so that the website can remember who you are, e.g. with the login credentials.
We use cookies in the following ways:
- To help us recognize you as a unique visitor, (just a number) when you return to our website. This would technically also allow us to match your preferred interests with specific content in our site. In practice we are not that technically savvy, so unlikely to use cookies  for this purpose.
- To compile anonymous aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our website. This helps us improve the background of our website.
Two types of cookies may be used on our website. The first are session cookies, which remain in the cookies file of your browser until you leave our site. The second are persistent cookies which remain in the cookie file of your browser for the life of the specific cookie. Most of our web pages also contain electronic images known as Web beacons that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. This helps us to formulate the offerings that we make on our site. Web beacons collect a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page from which the web beacon originates.
Disabling/Enabling cookies
You can accept or decline the use of cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. Please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of our website. To find out more on how to disable or enable cookies visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
A popup will appear the first time you visit our website, asking you for permission to collect your cookies. Once approved, we consider you allow us using you cookies till further request.
LEGITIMATE INTEREST
In some situations, we can use your data to reach our legitimate goals in a way which might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and which does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests, like sending you personalised offers following your purchase, and using your address details to send you promotional material that might interest you.
LEGAL COMPLIANCE
We may need to collect and process your data if required by the law.
QUESTIONS AND FURTHER UPDATES ON THIS NOTICE
If you have any question regarding this notice you can email us at: sales@hampers.co.uk
This notice was last updated on 16/05/2018. Please note Hay Hampers Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any change we may apply.
Sorry, we are fully booked for Christmas! We are taking orders for delivery from 11th January.
This year, Christmas may not be quite what we are all used to, but we can all send food and love to those we will be missing and connect with them in different ways. In these unprecedented times, we want to reassure you we care deeply about your gift purchase and provide a regularly updated Covid page here to provide guidance on how we are monitoring the situation in relation to our service.
Hay Hampers are passionate creators and suppliers of luxury wine and food gifts -not just at Christmas,  We have gifts for every occasion. We have a wide range of birthday gift hampers, or thank you gifts with delicious, gourmet food and the best wines are our specialism.  All our gifts are beautifully packaged and sent with free UK delivery including a proper gift card (we even inspire you with gift messages here). We cater bulk orders and bespoke hampers for our corporate business customers sending hamper gifts to employees or clients. We are passionate about customer service and will always do whatever we can to help you. Call, email, live chat, facebook message or try our help pages for assistance.
Our mission is to make gift giving an easy pleasure with our perfectly presented premium products! We hope your recipient enjoys their hamper and have a Very "Hampery" Christmas with one of our best-selling food and wine gifts include luxury cheese board selections for him. or a chocolate hamper for her. Try something different with our authentic range of Italian hampers with Prosecco for foodies. We also love our range of craft beer & snack gifts. Our range includes gin & whisky spirit gifts. We also have a range of traditional British foods, such as Port & Stilton, or Afternoon Tea gift, and special dietary requirements gifts such as Vegan hampers so you can find the best hamper gift for you.
Here to help
+
Contact Us
My Account
Personalised Greeting Card
Our guarantee
Corporate Customer Services
Shopping with us
PE10 9LQ
mothers day - easter hampers - fathers day gift hampers - birthday - breakfast in bed - birthday gifts - congratulations - corporate hampers - get well - gourmet dinners - hostess gifts - incentive and rewards - new baby - picnic - retirement - summer hampers - thank you - wedding anniversary - craft beer & wine gifts - chocolate hampers - mother's day - christmas meat hampers - christmas hampers ideas - christmas wine, beer and port gifts -  christmas hampers - xmas hamper 2017 - christmas black friday - christmas italian food hampers - christmas hampers for men - christmas luxury hampers - christmas cheese hampers - corporate christmas hampers - black friday -valentines gifts - valentine's day presents - valentine's chocolate gifts - valentine's cheese gifts - valentines hampers - recipient - price - all gifts - recipe - special offers - italy2eat - vintners
face
twitter
Instagram
Pinterest
Linkedin
Sign up now to our email newsletter to receive updates, offers and promotions!Enter your email below:
Newsletter
Sign up for newsletter
Subscribe
INFORMATION
Our Family Business
Help & FAQ
Terms & Conditions
Our Privacy Notice
The Taste House, Roman Bank, Bourne Lincolnshire PE10 9LQ
christmas hampers - christmas hamper gifts - corporate christmas hampers - chocolate flower gifts -  breakfast in bed - birthday gifts - birthday hampers - congratulations - corporate hampers - get well - gourmet dinners - hostess gifts - incentive and rewards - new baby - picnic - retirement - Xmas 2020 -  summer hampers - cheese hampers - father's day gifts - thank you - mothers day - wedding anniversary - easter gifts  - craft beer & wine gifts - chocolate hampers - mother's day - lactose free - kosher food gift hamper - equipped picnic back packs & cool bag hamper gifts - equipped wicker picnic hamper baskets - smoked salmon hampers - cured meat hamper - St Andrew's St David's St George's St Patrick's Day - spicy food hamper - wine hampers - food and wine hamper - wine and cheese  eid al-fitr gift hampers - hamper - wine and chocolate hampers - food and wine hampers  - low sugar - recipient - price - all gifts - recipe - special offers - italy2eat - vintners - producers - black friday - site map - gourmet game hamper
Site Map
Search Terms
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
Contact Us
Hay Hampers Ltd
The Taste House
Roman Bank
